[Music]
[音乐]
male estamos listos Yemeni dosa gracias
男性estamos listos也门dosa gracias
por assistir esta say Sione's totalmente
通过助手说西昂的总数
en castiana ha bro me ando kidding
恩·卡斯蒂安娜·哈·布罗
anyway occasionally I do give a talk in
无论如何，我偶尔也会讲话
Spanish but this time no we're all in on
西班牙文，但这次不，我们全力以赴
English right sure why not
英语正确，为什么不
so welcome to this afternoon I guess now
欢迎来到今天下午
this afternoon session on spring
春季下午
security for noobs and by the way that's
菜鸟的安全性和顺便说一句
not derogatory we're all noobs and far
不贬义我们都是菜鸟
more things than were experts right so
比专家说的还多
this is kind of meant to be an
这有点像是
introductory session kind of in general
介绍性会议一般
at a very quick quick pass through for
快速地通过
security in general and then diving
一般安全然后潜水
right into spring security and
进入Spring Security 和
application security and specifically I
应用安全性，特别是我
actually do want to get a a photo before
其实确实想拍张照片
I get started because I so often forget
我开始，因为我常常忘记
to do this so I need to prove to my boss
为此，我需要向老板证明
that I was actually here doing something
我实际上是在这里做某事
versus just sampling the the coffee
而不是只喝咖啡
scene here in Barcelona which by the way
巴塞罗那的现场
is quite excellent but we won't tell him
非常好，但我们不会告诉他
that okay so let's see if I can let's do
好的，让我们看看我是否可以做
two sides here was really terrible
双方都很糟糕
with my photography skills maybe one of
我的摄影技巧也许是其中之一
those turned out anyway so you know so
那些反正结果如此，所以你知道
if you need to reach me if you have
如果您需要联系我
questions comments or feedback I have a
问题评论或反馈我有一个
lot of material that I want to go
我想去的很多资料
through and I don't want to rush it but
通过，我不想着急，但
I do want to be pretty pretty methodical
我确实想变得有条不紊
about moving forward so that we can get
关于前进，以便我们可以
through all of this and hopefully have a
通过所有这些，希望有一个
bit of time for Q&amp;A at the end if not
如果没有的话，最后的问答时间
the best way to reach me is on Twitter I
最好的联系方式是在Twitter上
live on Twitter from the time I wake up
从我醒来起就在Twitter上直播
to the time I go to bed and sometimes in
到我上床睡觉的时间，有时
between so if you're not following me on
所以如果你不跟着我
Twitter why first why but secondly if
Twitter为什么第一个为什么，但是第二个如果
you would just follow me at em k Tech
你只要在em k Tech跟着我
and if you have any questions comments
如果您有任何问题评论
or feedback please do reach out to me
或反馈请与我联系
via Twitter preferably if you have
通过Twitter最好如果你有
questions comments or feedback and you
问题评论或反馈，您
don't want to share them with the whole
不想与所有人分享
world my direct messages are open so
世界，我的直接信息是开放的，所以
just DM me that's perfectly fine if you
DM我，如果你很好
if you don't like Twitter if you're not
如果你不喜欢Twitter，如果你不喜欢
on Twitter which by the way you should
在Twitter上，顺便说一句
be on Twitter but if you're not there
在Twitter上，但如果您不在那儿
I'm also a member of the slightly older
我也是年龄稍大的成员
and more established social network
和更完善的社交网络
called email is he doing on email okay
叫电子邮件，他在做电子邮件吗？
well I am still any mail I'm not quite
好吧，我仍然是任何邮件，我不太
as diligent about responding to email I
勤于回应电子邮件
do check it from time to time though so
确实不时检查一下
please do reach out there as well the
请也伸手去拿
two email addresses that I check the
我检查的两个电子邮件地址
least infrequently our mark at the
至少我们很少在
hecklers comm and M heckler at pivotal I
hecklers comm和M heckler在关键I
oh so disorder so Who am I and what
哦，如此混乱，所以我是谁？
makes me semi sort of pseudo almost
使我几乎半伪
partially qualified to talk about this I
我有资格谈论这个
have authored several blogs and blog
撰写了多个博客和博客
posts I've co-authored a couple of books
我曾合着几本书的文章
I contributed content and code to
我向
several other books some of which
其他几本书，其中一些
actually even recognize my contributions
甚至承认我的贡献
which was nice the rest of them well I
其余的人很好我
wasn't planning on living on the
不打算住在
royalties anyway so it's not a big deal
版税，所以没什么大不了的
I guess I am a frequent event speaker a
我想我经常参加活动
third or fourth time here at spring a oh
春季第三次或第四次哦
I think it's fourth now which is awesome
我认为现在已经是第四了
any first-timers yeah I hope I hope
是任何新手，是的，我希望我希望
you'll come back and I hope they'll let
你会回来的，我希望他们会让
me come back to it's just a great
我回到这很棒
great event and just gets better every
重大事件，每一次都会变得更好
year I am a Java champion and a Java one
年我是Java冠军和Java冠军
rock star and a few other you know
摇滚明星和其他一些你知道的
meaningless hordes I'm sorry they're not
无意义的部落，对不起，他们不是
meaningless but but anyway I attend and
没有意义，但无论如何我都会参加
have contributed to the Java community
为Java社区做出了贡献
for a long time plan to continue doing
长期计划继续做
so so if you had anything to do with the
因此，如果您与
recognitions I appreciate it thanks for
感谢我感谢
the vote of confidence I am a
我是一个信任票
professional problem solver
专业问题解决者
that's not my official title it's just
那不是我的正式头衔
what I do as do you right this is our
我所做的和您所做的一样，这是我们的
life
生活
but I am a spring developer and advocate
但我是一名春季开发者和倡导者
with pivotal so that's the official part
与关键，所以这是官方的一部分
so some takeaways for today and I guess
所以今天有一些外卖，我想
I'm gonna have to manually do that
我将不得不手动执行
that's so tough first I want to at least
首先很难，我至少要
give a bit of contextual background in
给出一些上下文背景
terms of an outside-in security profile
由内而外的安全配置文件的条款
kind of what we're talking about and
我们在说什么
again set that context for the rest of
再次为其余的内容设置背景
the exploration here we're gonna going
我们将要进行的探索
to talk a bit about system versus
谈谈系统与
application level security and what that
应用程序级别的安全性以及那
entails distinctions and differences
需要区别和差异
then we'll talk a bit about
那我们再谈一点
authentication and authorization or as I
身份验证和授权或作为我
like to say who's who in the zoo and who
想说谁在动物园里，谁在谁
does what to whom with what and when and
在何时何地向谁做什么
that's kind of important right we hear
这是我们重要的权利
terms thrown around an awful lot and
术语太多了
sometimes that are used interchangeably
有时可以互换使用
sometimes I slip up and use them
有时我会滑起来并使用它们
interchangeably so I'll try it my best
可互换，所以我会尽力而为
to make that distinction that again kind
再次做出那种区分
of helps with with clarity I think open
我认为很明确的帮助
ID Connect I know off - what do they do
我知道ID Connect-他们是做什么的
and what's the value we hear a lot about
我们听到很多什么价值
OAuth 2 not so much about open ID
OAuth 2与开放ID无关
connect but obviously it's in there and
连接，但显然它在那里
I'll you know explain kind of the
我会告诉你的
distinction with that as well and how
以及如何区别
they they came into being and will code
他们他们应运而生，并会编码
and I tend to narrate while I code so
在编写代码时，我倾向于叙述
I'll provide some of the background and
我将提供一些背景和
then we'll launch in and I'll continue
然后我们将启动，我将继续
to kind of guide through as we write
在撰写本文时提供指导
code because again that's how I
代码，因为这又是我的方式
internalize things best I think that
最好地内化事物，我认为
makes sense right we're used to dealing
说对了，我们习惯了
with code so it kind of helps to see how
使用代码，因此有助于了解如何
it applies directly to our to what we're
它直接适用于我们
we're creating
我们正在创造
so first the outside and security or as
所以首先是外部和安全性
I like to say sort of this this was a
我喜欢这样说
diagram that was created probably 2000
创建的图表大概是2000年
years ago I think
多年前，我认为
it's not been quite that long but it
没那么久，但是
feels like it it's still being
感觉它仍然在
propagated by the CISSP and I guess it
由CISSP传播，我猜是
has some merit I think conceptually it's
有一些优点我认为从概念上讲
not a bad thing to kind of look at
看起来不是一件坏事
things this way but in the age of cloud
这样的事情，但是在云时代
things have changed
事情变了
they've shuffled quite a bit and in some
他们已经洗牌了很多
ways inverted and in some ways certain
倒转的方式，在某种程度上是确定的
things that we viewed perhaps as
我们可能认为是的东西
sacrosanct in years past they're not
在过去的几年中神圣不可侵犯
necessarily that applicable anymore at
必然适用于
least not at a you know very extensive
至少不会，你知道的很广泛
level so in the old days when we had
水平，所以在过去，当我们有
physical facilities and physical data
物理设施和物理数据
centers and server rooms and and
中心和服务器机房以及
clusters and racks of servers and I mean
服务器的集群和机架，我的意思是
obviously there are servers somewhere
显然在某处有服务器
but many times we don't deal with those
但是很多时候我们不处理那些
right but in the old days when we had
是的，但是在过去，
all of that when we managed them
当我们管理它们时，所有这些
physically we typically in an
身体上我们通常在
organization dealt with things at a
组织在
policies procedure and awareness level
政策程序和意识水平
so we crafted these beautiful mounds of
所以我们精心制作了这些美丽的土堆
documentation and and policies that we
我们的文件和政策
applied toward everything in terms of a
适用于一切
security profile this kind of enveloped
安全配置文件这种笼罩的
our physical security who had access to
我们的人身安全
perhaps our installation and our
也许我们的安装和我们的
specific building and our server rooms
特定建筑物和我们的服务器机房
and things like that we carefully
和类似的事情，我们仔细
controlled our network stack you know
控制我们的网络堆栈
how how we dealt with ingress and egress
我们如何处理进出
in terms of data coming in and out of
在进出数据方面
our applications our our systems as a
我们的应用程序我们的系统
journal at a general level we secured
我们获得的一般水平的期刊
our servers so we had our server stack
我们的服务器，所以我们有了服务器堆栈
that we dealt with physically and
我们在身体上处理
configurationally is that a word but but
配置上是一个词，但是
we typically looked at things and and
我们通常看的东西和
drilled in to that level next on our
接下来深入到我们的那个级别
servers of course we're hosted our
当然，我们托管服务器
applications and our applications kind
应用程序和我们的应用程序种类
of enveloped the data that our
封装了我们的数据
applications use right it makes for a
应用使用权
great picture again this is a bit
很棒的照片，这有点
different in today's day and age because
今天的时代不同，因为
in many cases perhaps for instance we'll
例如，在很多情况下，我们会
have a data service that we're
有我们的数据服务
connecting to via a URI and that is
通过URI连接到
nowhere near where our applications are
距离我们的应用程序不远
being hosted we may not even know or
被托管，我们甚至可能不知道或
care where the instances of our
关心我们的实例
application at this point in time we're
此时的应用程序
running so I think it's good in terms of
运行，所以我认为这很好
a generic mental construct but it
通用的心理构造，但它
certainly doesn't hold
当然不成立
you know hold much water in terms of the
你知道在水方面
physical contact anymore again I think
我想身体再接触一次
it's useful mentally if you update it to
如果将其更新为
this century it is after all 2019 now so
毕竟这个世纪现在是2019年
a few general thoughts on system
关于系统的一些一般想法
security these are I'm gonna hit these
安全这些是我要击中这些
very quickly because again you could do
很快，因为您可以再次做
entire talks on any one or a couple of
关于任何一个或几个的整个谈话
these and we don't have that much time
这些，我们没有那么多时间
sadly but I do think it's important at
可悲的是，但我认为这很重要
least though that out there many of you
至少尽管有很多人
already have these in place many of you
已经有这些了，你们很多
don't you know I still generally say
你不知道我还是会说
it's 2019 but these things take time
现在是2019年，但是这些事情需要时间
right especially in large organizations
对大型组织尤其如此
but you should have some kind of
但是你应该有一些
password and access hygiene you should
您应该输入密码和访问卫生
have some method of controlling access
有一些控制访问的方法
controlling who can access your systems
控制谁可以访问您的系统
and to what extent in what ways
在什么程度上以什么方式
two-factor authentication or
两因素验证或
multi-factor authentication is very
多因素认证非常
important right the more if you have
重要的权利，如果你有
multiple factors it's not just based on
不只是基于多种因素
what you know you can't just somehow
你知道你不能只是某种方式
compromise a person's password and you
泄露一个人的密码，您
have access to everything you should
有权使用您应有的一切
have seen authorizations so many times
看了很多次授权
we have dealt with in the past the
我们过去已经处理过
principle of least privilege which is a
最小特权原则是
good thing in concept again once once
概念上的好事一次
again in concept but if you have a
再次在概念上，但如果你有一个
five-minute changes that takes five
五分钟的变更需要五分钟
weeks to get approvals and
数周才能获得批准，并且
authorizations to deploy perhaps that's
部署授权可能就是
not keeping you competitive right so I
不能保持你的竞争力，所以我
always tend to kind of go toward the
总是倾向于去
saint's authorizations you don't want to
圣人的授权，你不想
throw open the doors and give everyone
敞开大门，给大家
everything but you should have a way of
一切，但你应该有办法
giving enough privileges and enough
给予足够的特权和足够的
permissions to where real work can get
获得实际工作的权限
done in an expedient fashion logging and
以方便的方式进行日志记录和
auditing is very important because when
审核非常重要，因为何时
things happen is invariably things do
事情总是发生
you need to be able to quickly identify
您需要能够快速识别
trace the root cause and fix right so
找出根本原因并进行正确修复
it's very important that we have good
重要的是我们要有好
monitoring and logging is throughout our
监视和记录是我们的全部工作
systems entire systems why our
系统整个系统，为什么我们
encryption is very important in the old
在过去，加密非常重要
days we typically looked at things like
几天里，我们通常会看诸如
HTTP as being high overhead right they
HTTP是高开销的，他们
incurred a big cost we didn't want to do
付出了我们不想做的大笔费用
that my goodness that would be a huge
我的天哪会是巨大的
performance it turns out it's not so
性能事实并非如此
much there are a couple reasons you want
你有很多原因
wire encryption one is for the cosmetic
有线加密之一是用于化妆品
reason and that if you serve
原因，如果你服务
applications up via webpage and you do
通过网页申请，您可以
it perhaps through Chrome Google Chrome
它可能通过Chrome浏览器
will identify things that aren't served
会识别出没有送达的东西
up via HTTPS as
通过HTTPS作为
insecure you don't necessarily want your
没有安全感的人不一定要
users to be freaked out all the time
用户一直被吓坏了
with this app is insecure
这个程序是不安全的
this site is unsecure so that's passe
这个网站是不安全的，所以过去了
metic more than anything but it's also
功夫比什么都重要，但它也
in actual practical matter coming back
在实际问题上又回来了
to the performance hit CPU why is it's
对性能造成影响的CPU为什么是
about a 1% performance that Google
大约是Google的1％
converted everything to HTTPS and found
将所有内容都转换为HTTPS并找到
1% in terms of network performance hit
对网络性能的影响为1％
it was about 2% so this is negligible
大约是2％，所以可以忽略不计
stuff to have encrypted communication
加密通讯的东西
via the wire so this just frankly should
通过电线，所以坦率地说，这应该
be done across the board you should
应该全盘完成
store your secrets securely this is very
安全地存储您的秘密，这非常
important you know so many times we
重要的是你知道很多次
don't necessarily guard our secrets well
不一定很好地保护我们的秘密
but the things like hashey core console
但是像hashey core console这样的东西
for instance this is so easy to do
例如，这很容易做到
anymore that it seems again rather
再次看起来
pointless and silly not to
没有意义和愚蠢的
you should also encrypt your data at
您还应该在以下位置加密数据
rest it does no good to secure the
休息并不能确保安全
communications pipeline if if all of
通讯管道，如果全部
your jewels your your crown jewels are
你的珠宝你的皇冠珠宝是
out there exposed because if someone
外面暴露出来，因为如果有人
gains access to your network whether
是否可以访问您的网络
that's a disgruntled employee which by
那是一个心怀不满的员工
the way that's a huge one in terms of
就这一点而言，这是一个巨大的方式
security compromises that's the top of
安全妥协是最重要的
the pile or if someone does actually
堆，或者如果有人真的
gain in unauthorized access to your
擅自访问您的
network you don't want to leave that
网络，你不想离开那个
data sitting off the unencrypted for
未加密的数据
easy harvest right so again these are
容易收获，所以这些又是
all things that could be their own talk
所有可能都是他们自己的话题
by themselves we don't have time for
靠我们自己没有时间
that so another time another talk and
所以下次再谈
we'll just go from there
我们就从那里去
drilling in a little bit more at this
在此多钻一些
point to application security or much
指向应用程序安全性或很多
more at this point let's talk spring
在这一点上，让我们谈谈春天
security spring security is an
安全性Spring Security 性是
open-source framework you can use it
您可以使用开源框架
with any Java or well JVM based
与任何基于Java或基于JVM的
application typically you see it used in
应用程序通常会在
conjunction with Spring Framework
与Spring Framework结合
applications and Spring Beach actually
应用程序和Spring Beach实际上
bring some nice auto configuration to
带来一些不错的自动配置
the mix as well so that's kind of the
混合以及这样的
the home but it certainly doesn't
家，但它肯定不会
require that but spring security brings
要求但Spring Security 带来
a lot a lot to the table and there's a
桌子上很多东西，还有一个
lot to it right anything that you have
正确处理任何您拥有的东西
that it is meant to guard against a
旨在防止
bunch of different attack vectors and
一堆不同的攻击向量和
and bad eventualities necessarily has
坏事必然有
some complexity I like to take it up to
我喜欢一些复杂性
a higher level because at a higher level
更高的层次，因为更高的层次
I think it's pretty simple and even that
我认为这很简单，即使那样
I've streamlined things but these are
我已经简化了事情，但是这些是
my mind the the the first among equals
我的想法是第一个等于
the top 3 things you should kind of
您应该注意的三件事
understand to to grok house spring
知道去春天的小屋
security generally works starting with
安全通常从
spring security 5 we now have an HDTV
Spring Security 5我们现在有高清电视
firewall many times malformed URIs are
防火墙多次出现格式错误的URI
responsible for a lot a lot of
负责很多
compromises right so if you can filter
妥协的权利，所以如果您可以过滤
out those malformed Erie's your you've
那些畸形的伊利是你的
gone a long way to making your
让您走了很长一段路
application secure the HTTP firewall
应用程序保护HTTP防火墙
checks for any malformed URIs this
检查是否有任何格式错误的URI
guards those requests and life goes
守卫着这些要求，生命就过去了
merrily along and it's secure by default
很高兴，并且默认情况下是安全的
so it's at the highest security level
因此处于最高安全级别
the highest level of rigor and you can
最高的严格度，您可以
back that off you can tweak it certainly
支持它，您当然可以对其进行调整
you have adjustments that can be made
您可以进行调整
but again and this is one thing I want
但这又是我想要的一件事
to keep mentioning I probably will keep
继续提我可能会继续
mentioning is it's the most secure by
提到这是最安全的
default right we're not Mongo any Mongo
默认权限我们不是Mongo任何Mongo
folks out there I say that and I'll
乡亲们，我这么说，我会
occasionally kind of like poke fun at
偶尔有点像在戳戳
friends but the fact of the matter is
朋友，但事实是
the worst offenses with Mongo are us
Mongo最糟糕的进攻是我们
right we all want something easy to use
对，我们都想要一些易于使用的东西
with minimal configuration and then when
以最小的配置，然后
somebody gives that to us and we don't
有人给我们，我们不
take the time to configure it and
花时间配置它
something bad happens we point the
我们指出了一些不好的事情
finger elsewhere and and much of the
手指和其他地方
problem with Mongo is that frankly we
蒙哥的问题是，坦率地说，我们
didn't none of us bother to secure it so
我们所有人都不费心去保护它
that's not a good thing right
那不是一件好事吧
we took the opposite approach and Spring
我们采取了相反的方法，而Spring
Framework spring security all of the
框架Spring 安全的所有
various spring portfolio of components
各种Spring 零件组合
and products are opinionated and the
和产品是有思想的，
opinion of Spring Framework is you
Spring Framework的观点是
should start off from a position of the
应该从
highest level security and back that
最高级别的安全性
often adjust that where needed
经常在需要的地方进行调整
so the HTTP firewall is locked down
因此HTTP防火墙已锁定
pretty tightly or as tightly as possible
紧密地或尽可能紧密地
from the get-go the next part to be
从一开始，下一部分
aware of is the security filter chain
知道的是安全过滤器链
and this is kind of the secret sauce in
这是里面的秘密调味料
my opinion right because once a request
我的意见正确，因为一旦提出要求
passes the HTTP firewall it goes through
通过它穿过的HTTP防火墙
a series of filters and you establish
一系列的过滤器，您可以建立
these filters and provide criteria that
这些过滤器并提供标准
if a filter a particular filter is met
如果某个过滤器符合特定过滤器
then it the request pops out of the
然后请求从弹出
filter chain in this process accordingly
相应地在此过程中过滤链
right so as soon as it makes a match
对，所以一旦匹配
then it's processed if it goes all the
然后处理所有的
way through the chain and
通过链的方式和
match what happens its discarded so
匹配发生了什么，将其丢弃
again that other level of security comes
再次提到其他安全级别
into being and then you have request
成，然后你有要求
headers the internet and I by the way
头互联网和我的方式
I'll get into the security filtering a
我将进入安全过滤
bit more here momentarily and then of
暂时在这里多一点，然后
course we'll see it in action as well
当然，我们也会在行动中看到它
the internet Engineering Task Force
互联网工程任务组
dictates certain things that can be
决定某些可以
included and request headers and these
包含和请求标头以及这些
are areas that can be used to button
是可以用来按纽的区域
down again security to to make sure that
再次降低安全性以确保
again from that position of security or
再次从安全位置出发
strength that you can eliminate a lot of
可以消除很多力量的力量
potential attack vectors and I'll cover
潜在的攻击媒介，我将介绍
that as again as we get into it a little
再次，当我们进入它一点
bit more and show some of the different
多一点，展示一些不同
headers that are on by default or can be
标头在默认情况下处于启用状态或可以是
tweaked in spring security as well so
在Spring Security 性方面也进行了调整
again there's more but these are I think
再有更多，但我认为这些
again the first among peers and
再一次在同行中
certainly the most important to kind of
当然，最重要的是
dive in and get started before I forget
在我忘记之前潜入并开始
as I likely will there is a workshop
我可能会有一个讲习班
this afternoon on spring security and
今天下午关于Spring Security 和
open ID Connect so if you hadn't made
打开ID Connect，所以如果您没有做
plans to take that end I would encourage
计划为此目的，我鼓励
you to do so as kind of a continuation
您这样做是一种延续
of this talk and then Joe Grandda who is
这次演讲，然后是乔·格兰达
one of our security ninjas on our secret
我们秘密中的安全忍者之一
spring security team is giving a talk
Spring Security 团队发表演讲
tomorrow which goes much more in-depth I
明天我会更深入
would strongly encourage you to sit in
会强烈鼓励你坐在
on that because this will take you up to
之所以这样，是因为它将带您
a point but Joe will take you much much
要说一点，但乔会带给你很多
farther than that
比那更远
so please do make plans to attend that
所以请做好计划参加
tomorrow as well so the request
明天也是如此
filtering and again this is somewhat
过滤，这又有点
simplified as well but it's pretty
也简化了，但是很漂亮
straightforward right a filter chain
直截了当的过滤器链
proxy come is comprises multiple or well
代理来是由多个还是很好的
potentially multiple security filter
潜在的多重安全过滤器
chains typically you'll have one but you
连锁店通常会有一个，但是你
do have the possibility of having
确实有可能
multiples but in most cases what you
倍数，但大多数情况下
basically have is a series of filters
基本上有一系列的过滤器
that are passed you know that our
通过了，你知道我们
request passes through until again it
请求通过直到再次通过
makes that match or not and then
使匹配或不匹配，然后
something happens right again simple
事情再次发生简单
concept very neat in an elegant
概念非常整齐优雅
execution so let's code and I'm yeah
执行，让我们编码，我是
already I'm getting hot so I feel like
我已经很热了，所以我觉得
I'm in that hot seat already but I
我已经在那个热座位上了，但是我
promise
诺言
I promise that's as far as I'll strip
我保证那是我要剥离的范围
okay so this is a family-friendly
好吧，这是一个家庭友好的
session okay so it's by the way I always
会议还可以，所以我总是这样
I always try to dress appropriately for
我总是试着穿得合适
a session so I wore my getting started
一个会议，所以我穿了我的入门
with spring security shirt here I think
我觉得这里有Spring Security 衫
that's good advice if you're not a
如果您不是
Douglas Adams fan again why go read the
道格拉斯·亚当斯迷再次为何去读
checkers Guide to the galaxy please
跳棋星系指南，请
you'll you'll appreciate it
你会你会感激的
okay so let's get started
好吧，让我们开始吧
does everyone recognize this site this
每个人都认识这个网站吗
has changed of late if you haven't been
如果你最近没去过
here in a while this may look a bit
在一段时间里这可能看起来有点
different to you but that's good right
与您不同，但这是很好的权利
change is good
有改变是好事
if if anyone is sitting out there saying
如果有人坐在那里说
who moved my cheese and is wondering
谁动了我的奶酪，想知道
what happened to the old spring
旧春天发生了什么
initializer this is a new improved
初始化程序，这是一个新的改进
version if there's something that you
版本，如果你有东西
find missing or that you wish were there
发现失踪或您希望在那里
again we're taking feedback so please do
再次，我们正在收集反馈，所以请
give us that feedback but in general
给我们反馈，但总的来说
it's just a nice neat clean interface
这只是一个很好的干净界面
now so very cool I'm gonna stay down the
现在太酷了，我要保持冷静
middle let's see how I'm doing on time
中段，让我们看看我的准时情况
this is good so I should be okay
这很好，我应该可以
I'm gonna stay down the middle here but
我要留在这中间
you have options to create spring and
您可以选择创建spring和
spring boot based micro services here
基于Spring Boot的微服务
I'm gonna stay with maven and Java but
我将继续使用Maven和Java，但
again if it makes you happy to do Gradle
如果让您高兴地做Gradle，请再次
on Kotlin which I frequently do this
在Kotlin上，我经常这样做
well that's fine too or groovy
好吧，还是很好
what-have-you I'm gonna stay with the
你要怎么办？
current version of spring boot which is
Spring Boot的当前版本是
now 2 dot 1.5 as I'm yesterday
我现在是2点1.5
woot wow that doesn't seem okay I know
哇哇，那似乎不行，我知道
I'm a little geeky but I mean this is
我有点怪异，但这是
good stuff folks all right so two not
好人，好吧，所以两个不
1.5 I'm gonna change this to the
1.5我将其更改为
hecklers because I can and I'm gonna
I徒，因为我可以，我要
step through a couple different
经历几个不同的步骤
scenarios here because I think it helps
这里的场景，因为我认为这有帮助
build that foundation that basic
建立基础
security foundation I'm gonna start with
我将以安全基础开始
form based authentication or user ID
基于表单的身份验证或用户ID
password right and that is in many cases
密码正确，在许多情况下
what many applications use that's enough
有多少应用程序使用就足够了
right that's that's sufficient so I'm
对，那就足够了，我
gonna call this s sec for spring
春季要叫这个秒
security form and I'm just going to
安全表格，我正要去
bring in a few dependencies that I'm
带来一些我依赖的东西
gonna use I'm gonna stay with the basic
要用我会坚持基本
imperative spring MVC type of
命令式Spring MVC类型
application certainly there's a reactive
应用程序肯定会有反应
capability as well but I'm going to keep
能力，但我会继续
it as plain vanilla as I can so I can
尽可能地像普通香草一样
focus
焦点
Pacific Leon the stuff I want to focus
太平洋莱昂我想集中的东西
on and then I'm going to bring in the
然后我要带上
dependency for spring security that's it
依赖于Spring Security就是这样
so we'll get started there and we'll
所以我们将从那里开始，我们将
save that down and then I'm just going
保存下来，然后我就去
to go to my desktop and we'll unzip that
转到我的桌面，我们将其解压缩
and we'll open that in my favorite IDE
我们将在我最喜欢的IDE中打开它
NetBeans I'm kidding again yes
NetBeans我又在开玩笑了
NetBeans is awesome I you know again I
NetBeans很棒，我又知道了
pick on my friends if any NetBeans users
如果有NetBeans用户，请选择我的朋友
out there I certainly I love NetBeans
我当然很喜欢NetBeans
it's a great ide works well with spring
这是一个伟大的思想，与春天相得益彰
food applications eclipse as well
食品应用也日食
eclipse is a great Eclipse is an IDE I'm
eclipse是一个很棒的Eclipse是一个IDE
kidding I mean we have spring tool suite
开玩笑，我的意思是我们有 spring tool suite
built on Eclipse actually are built with
在Eclipse上构建的实际上是用
Eclipse in conjunction with which
Eclipse与之结合
actually has some great cloud deployment
实际上有一些很棒的云部署
capabilities every time a friend of mine
每次有我的朋友都能胜任
shows me that I just it looks so good
告诉我我看起来很好
but IntelliJ fits my my workflow really
但是IntelliJ确实适合我的工作流程
well so I tend to kind of stay with that
好吧，所以我倾向于留下来
I'm actually going to take this into
我实际上要考虑到这一点
presentation mode which does some funny
演示模式，有些有趣
things when I have multiple projects
我有多个项目时的事情
loaded but it just looks really nice and
加载，但看起来真的很好，
nice and clean inner so let's let's just
内在干净整洁，让我们开始吧
start off yeah so there we go
开始，是的，所以我们走了
so the first thing I'm going to do is
所以我要做的第一件事是
just create a rest controller and we'll
只需创建一个 rest controller ，我们将
call this class our form form controller
将此类称为我们的表单表单控制器
and we're just going to keep it pretty
而且我们要保持漂亮
simple again on right off the bat so I'm
马上又简单了，所以我
going to do a get mapping for slash
将进行斜线的获取映射
everyone because I want to have everyone
每个人，因为我想拥有每个人
be able to access a particular page and
能够访问特定页面
I'm just going to again keep this simple
我将再次保持这个简单
so we'll just say for get every one
所以我们只说得到每个
return hello everyone everyone okay
返回大家好大家好
super simple here I also want to create
我也想在这里创建超级简单
an admin capability or an admin page so
管理员功能或管理员页面
I'm just going to do a get mapping slash
我只是要做一个映射斜线
admin string admin only and return and
admin字符串admin仅返回，并返回
let's see we'll just do a h1
让我们看看我们会做一个h1
ministry door page / h1 greetings
部门门页/ h1问候
[Music]
[音乐]
admin admin okay okay so again really
管理员管理员好的好的，所以再次
simple stuff let's go ahead and rerun
简单的东西，让我们继续并重新运行
this or run this I guess for the first
这个或运行这个，我想第一个
time out and I'm going to switch now to
超时，我现在要切换到
a terminal I use HTTP pi instead of curl
我使用HTTP pi而不是curl的终端
because it's as they call it curl for
因为就像他们所说的
humans I like it because it formats my
我喜欢它，因为它可以格式化我的
stuff really nicely so if I do a colon
东西真的很好，所以如果我做一个冒号
and again you can leave off certain
再一次，你可以离开某些
things which for lazy coder like me
对于像我这样的懒惰编码员来说
that's a wonderful thing it seems
看来这是一件奇妙的事情
localhost if you don't provide it so
本地主机（如果您不提供）
we'll just do this and actually let's
我们就这样做，实际上，让我们
see a I said everyone's everyone
看到我说每个人都
everyone and this is exactly what should
大家，这正是应该的
happen right because we have spring
发生正确的事，因为我们有春天
security dependency on our class path
对我们的类路径的安全依赖
and it's saying hey look you said you
这是说嘿，看你说你
wanted to secured I'm gonna go with the
想确保我要去
default most secure position I can based
我可以设定的默认最安全位置
upon the information you've given me
根据你给我的信息
which isn't much admittedly at this
在这个上并没有什么大不了的
point but it's going to lock down my
点，但它会锁定我的
endpoints and this gives me a chance to
端点，这给了我机会
show you a couple things some of these
给你看几件事
headers I was talking about so one of
我正在谈论的标题，其中之一
the things by default the spring
春天的东西
security does is set things to no sniff
安全所做的事情是无嗅
right we want that no stiff in the
是的，我们希望不要僵硬
request header because that means that
请求标头，因为那意味着
your browser or your user agent will not
您的浏览器或用户代理不会
sniff the content and say smells like a
嗅内容，说闻起来像
JPEG let me go ahead and render that for
JPEG让我继续进行渲染
you because what happens then is you
你，因为那会发生什么
might have a script or something
可能有脚本或其他内容
nefarious embedded in that JPEG right
JPEG内嵌的恶意内容
you don't want that to happen so again
你不希望那样的事情再次发生
from that position of security we start
从安全的立场出发
off with no sniff we also have X frame
没有嗅探，我们也有X框架
options set to deny and what that does
选项设置为拒绝，这是做什么的
is ensure that you don't have frames
确保没有框架
support in your browser in particular so
在您的浏览器中尤其如此
an invisible or a transparent frame
不可见或透明的框架
can't be sitting on top of a button or a
不能坐在按钮上方或
link so that when you click on it it
链接，以便当您单击它时
does something other than what you would
做其他事情而不是你想要的
expect it to do because that invisible
期望它会做，因为那看不见
frame is there to capture that click
框架在那里捕获点击
that's what's known as clickjacking so
这就是所谓的点击劫持
hijacking that click you don't want that
劫持您不想要的点击
so you tend to set this to deny or
因此您倾向于将此设置为拒绝或
spring security does that for you on
Spring Security为您做到这一点
your behalf you also have cross-site
您代表您也有跨网站
scripting protection by default turned
默认情况下已启用脚本保护
on so again these are things that you
在这些又是你
get free out-of-the-box if you're using
如果您正在使用，可立即获得免费
a content delivery network you may need
您可能需要的内容交付网络
to tweak that particular
调整特定的
that last one these cross-site scripting
最后一个这些跨站点脚本
but again based upon what limited
但还是基于有限的条件
information we've given spring security
我们提供的Spring Security 信息
at this point it's configured very nice
至此，它的配置非常好
and secure it's also telling us right
并确保它也告诉我们正确的
off the bat that we actually was young
其实我们还很年轻
so we're unauthorized add to something
所以我们是未经授权的添加
look at that for a second we're
看一秒钟，我们
unauthorized we've tried to hit an end
未经授权，我们试图结束
point that we don't have access to at
指出我们无法访问
this point or wait shouldn't we right
这一点或等待我们不应该对
well the thing is again based upon the
嗯，事情还是基于
limited information we gave spring
我们给春天的信息有限
security when this application started
此应用程序启动时的安全性
it said look I'll create a user account
它说，看起来，我将创建一个用户帐户
and I'll give a or I'll generate a
我会给一个或我会生成一个
security password we didn't provide that
我们没有提供的安全密码
therefore we're trying to hit that and
因此，我们正在努力实现这一目标，
we're unauthorized
我们是未经授权的
so let me go back here now and do a dash
所以让我现在回到这里做一个破折号
dash off right with user and this
与用户冲刺而这
terribly long generated password and
生成的密码非常长，并且
then I'll try again so everyone and now
然后我会再试一次，所以每个人现在
the sudden we see this we've got hello
突然我们看到这个，我们打招呼
everyone so we are getting there right
大家，所以我们要正确到达那里
now what happens if we try to hit that
现在，如果我们尝试达到目标会发生什么
instead of the slash everyone slash
而不是每个人都斜线
admin well here's the bad news right we
好的，这是个坏消息，我们
haven't we haven't provided any way to
我们还没有提供任何方式
to determine authorization for various
确定各种授权
different endpoints so right now we have
不同的端点，所以现在我们有了
access to everything if we have access
如果我们有权访问所有内容
to anything so let's go and we'll
任何东西，让我们走吧，我们会
address that next so let's see the first
解决下一个问题，让我们看看第一个
thing I want to do is is configure my
我想做的是配置我的
security profile just a bit so I'm going
安全配置文件，所以我要走了
to enable web security and we'll create
启用网络安全，我们将创建
a class called security security config
称为安全性安全配置的类
config yeah typoing hype fast and
配置是的，快速输入打字错误和
sometimes I type oh fast as well so and
有时我也会快速输入哦，所以
I'm going to extend our web security
我将扩展我们的网络安全
configure it after which again is how we
配置它之后，这又是我们的方式
override that basic defined or
覆盖该基本定义或
predefined security that spring security
预定义的安全性带来了安全性
and spring boot makes in automatically
spring boot 自动插入
for us the auto config so the first
对我们来说，自动配置
thing I'm going to do is is override my
我要做的是覆盖我的
configure method here and this allows me
在这里配置方法，这使我
to see let mean that down just a little
看到让我们意味着下降了一点
bit so I have a little more room here
有点，所以我在这里还有更多的空间
this allows me to configure my
这使我可以配置我的
authorization I'll come back to that in
授权，我将回到
a moment but what I want to do first is
片刻，但我首先要做的是
authenticate now again I guess I need to
现在再次进行身份验证，我想我需要
come back to briefly touch this off
回来简单地谈一下
indication versus authorization they
指示与授权
sound just close enough alike that again
声音又足够接近
it's easy to get your tongue tangled and
很容易使您的舌头纠结，
say the wrong one but authorization
说错了但授权
excuse me authentication CI deterrent
请问身份验证CI威慑力
authentication is defining that you are
身份验证定义您
who you say you are so what's your name
你说的是谁，你叫什么名字
sir Michael Marcus Oh excellent
迈克尔·马库斯先生，太好了
likewise okay so Marcos can you preview
好的，Marcos可以预览
are you well hopefully you can you can
你希望你可以吗
prove that you are who you say you are
证明你就是你所说的
so you can access this application
因此您可以访问此应用程序
that's authentication now do you have
那就是身份验证
access to a particular endpoint that's
访问特定的端点
authorization deed are you authorized to
授权书，您是否有权
access this resource right so we're
正确访问此资源，所以我们
gonna start off and create a beam right
要开始并创建一个光束
and I need a user detail service I need
并且我需要一个用户详细信息服务
to create one so we'll just call this
创建一个，所以我们称之为
authentication this method and I'm going
验证此方法，我要
to create a couple of users here so user
在这里创建几个用户
let's see user details Marcos see okay
让我们看看用户详细信息Marcos认为还好
that effective user dot builder and I'm
那个有效的用户点生成器，我
going to let's see I'll do a user named
让我们来看一个名为“
Marcos and password well I'm gonna have
我要有Marcos和密码
to use you as the bad example so you
用你作为坏榜样，所以你
know yeah usually that's me which is
知道，通常这就是我
kind of appropriate because I'm a mark
有点合适，因为我是商标
too so so we'll just start off with
也是如此，所以我们将从
password password and let's see we'll do
密码密码，让我们来看看
a let's see roles and user will keep you
让我们来看看角色和用户会留住你
at user because right now well we're
在用户那里，因为现在我们很好
taking this slowly and we'll build that
慢慢来，我们会建立
user now I need another user here and
用户，现在我需要另一个用户
what's your name ma'am Lori Lau are ie
刘小姐你叫什么名字
okay alright so we can do that Lori
好吧，所以我们可以做到
pleasure to meet you
很高兴认识你
let's see user dot builder and user name
让我们看看用户点构建器和用户名
Laurie password and we'll say Lori's
Laurie的密码，我们会说Lori的
password hygiene is a bit better than
密码卫生比
yours you need to level up but this is a
您需要升级，但这是一个
good start right okay so this will be a
好的开始好吧，所以这将是一个
strong password it's just a demo okay I
强大的密码，只是一个演示好吗
could create a really nice tough one but
可以创造出一个非常好的硬汉，但是
then I have to retype that each time and
然后我必须每次重新输入
that's just terrible it slows me down
太可怕了，这让我慢下来
and we want to make sure we get through
我们要确保我们通过
this right so
这样吧
let's see I want Laurie to be a user and
让我们看看我希望Laurie成为用户，
also an admin all right so let's see
还可以的管理员，让我们来看看
oops there we go doc build and there we
哎呀，我们去了doc build，在那里，我们
go so now what I'm gonna do at this
现在走吧，我该怎么办
point is I just want to show what we
关键是我只想展示我们
have here so let's see Marcos password
在这里，让我们看看Marcos密码
and then we'll do a plus password there
然后我们在那输入一个加密码
we go and then I'm just going to
我们去，然后我就去
duplicate that so we can get Laurie's
复制，以便我们可以得到劳里的
password here and just show it so we can
在这里输入密码，然后显示出来即可
see what we're dealing with Laurie's
看看我们正在处理劳里的
password okay and then I want to return
密码还可以，然后我想返回
new I'm gonna create an in-memory user
我要创建一个内存中的用户
details manager which is a type of user
一种用户的详细信息管理器
detail service whether you're backing to
详细服务，无论您是否支持
something like spring data JDBC or LDAP
像Spring数据JDBC或LDAP之类的东西
or what-have-you these are all similar
或你有什么都相似
constructs they work similarly I'm just
它们的工作方式相似，我只是
gonna keep it simple here now again for
现在要在这里再次保持简单
the purposes of our demo and we're off
演示的目的，我们出发了
and running there so we have our
并在那里运行，所以我们有
authentication almost and I want to do
认证差不多，我想做
something here just so I can show you
这里有些东西，以便我可以告诉你
that we're not quite there yet I'm gonna
我们还没有到那儿，我要
go ahead and restart this I mean it
继续并重新启动这个，我的意思是
looks pretty good at this point right so
在这一点上看起来还不错，所以
let's see what happens when we try to
让我们看看当我们尝试
login I'm actually going to go to a page
登录我实际上要去一个页面
here so let's see localhost 8080 ah now
在这里，让我们看看localhost 8080啊
this is nice because out of the box
这很好，因为开箱即用
spring security will give you a login
Spring Security会给您登录
and logout page just pre-configured you
和注销页面只是预先配置好了
can obviously create your own but you
显然可以创建自己的，但你
need some mechanism for doing this and
需要一些机制来做到这一点，
if you fail to provide this it's
如果您无法提供此信息，
provided for you so let's see marcos and
提供给您，让我们来看看marcos和
password now we're getting a problem
密码，现在我们遇到了问题
here so let's go back and take a look
在这里，让我们回头看看
and let me scroll back through this and
让我回滚一下
it will tell us pretty nicely pretty
它会告诉我们非常漂亮
clearly what the problem is right out of
清楚地解决了什么问题
the gate we have a bit of an issue
门，我们有一个问题
actually it's right here there's no
其实就在这里
password encoder mapped and if we go
密码编码器映射，如果我们去
back up here and look let's see if I can
备份到这里，让我们看看是否可以
scroll back I've I got things nice and
向后滚动我已经感觉很好
big for visibility but it makes things a
可见度很大，但它使事情变得
little harder to find so let's see yeah
很难找到，所以让我们看看
here we go
开始了
so if we see our passwords here they
所以如果我们在这里看到密码
look suspiciously like clear text that's
看起来像是可疑的明文
because they're clear text that's a
因为它们是清晰的文字
problem right we don't want that one
问题权，我们不想要那个
because we don't store things in clear
因为我们没有把东西清楚地存储
text two because we need to assume that
文字二，因为我们需要假设
there will be some kind of an encoder
会有某种编码器
and decoder that is used to match this
和用于匹配此内容的解码器
which we haven't specified yet this is a
我们还没有指定，这是一个
bit of a problem so let's go ahead and
有点问题，让我们继续前进，
create a an encoder let's see so private
创建一个编码器让我们来看看如此私密
final password encoder will call this PW
最终的密码编码器将调用此PW
encoder equals password encoder
编码器等于密码编码器
factories that create delegating
创建委托的工厂
password encoder now what this does this
现在密码编码器这是做什么的
little bit of code here is very nice
这里的一点代码非常好
because this is a bit of future proofing
因为这是未来的证明
that we have so right out of the gate
以至于我们走出了大门
you can see that the default is bcrypt
您可以看到默认值为bcrypt
for an encoder decoder which is bad
对于坏的编码器解码器
right that's pretty good starting out
对，刚开始很好
right now but we also support certain
现在，但我们也支持某些
older hashing capabilities because
较旧的哈希功能，因为
that's those are still in widespread use
那就是那些仍在广泛使用的
sadly but it's a fact of life
可悲的是，这是生活中的事实
and then of course we think include
然后我们当然认为包括
things like PK pbkdf2 I never get that
像PK pbkdf2之类的东西我从来没有得到过
right I have to like pbkdf2 just doesn't
对，我不得不喜欢pbkdf2
roll off the tongue right s crypt and
从舌头右下窝滚下来，
what-have-you but we also have kind of
你有什么，但我们也有
future proof this so if there's an
未来证明这一点，所以如果有
additional mechanism for encryption
加密的附加机制
coming down the road that we want to
走在我们想要的道路上
support we can incorporate it here and
支持，我们可以在这里合并
simply with a user being a logging in we
只需用户登录
can update and refresh to a newer
可以更新和刷新到较新的版本
encryption mechanisms which is really
真正的加密机制
nice right transparent and future proof
不错的权利透明和未来的证明
so I like to show that because I think
所以我想表明这一点，因为我认为
that's a pretty pretty good thing so we
那是一件相当不错的事情，所以我们
need to let's see back here there's our
需要让我们回头看看这里是我们的
encoder so what I want to do at this
编码器，所以我想在这里做
point is just take my encoder and do an
重点就是拿我的编码器并做一个
encode and we'll encode our passwords
编码，我们将对密码进行编码
here and we'll try it again and we'll
在这里，我们将再次尝试，我们将
see what we get dot and code oops and
看看我们得到点和代码哎呀，
now we should be a little bit better off
现在我们应该会好一点
than we were momentarily a moment ago
比我们片刻前
and actually while that's coming up I'm
而实际上，在即将来临的时候
going to go ahead and do the rest of
将继续进行其余的工作
this because all I've talked at this
这是因为我在这方面的所有讨论
point is authentication I haven't done
关键是我还没有完成身份验证
anything in terms of authorization so
任何授权方面的内容
we've we've done nothing in terms of
我们在以下方面一无所获
determining who gets where we've set the
确定谁到达了我们设置的位置
stage for that with the roles that we
我们扮演的角色
defined when we created each of the two
当我们创建两个的时候定义
accounts
帐目
but we've not filtered for that all
但是我们还没有过滤全部
right so let's take our HTTP and we'll
对，所以让我们采用HTTP，我们将
do a an authorized request and by the
提出授权请求，并由
way when you set up the security filter
设置安全筛选器的方式
chain always go from the most specific
链总是从最具体的
to the least specific because again as
最不具体的原因是
soon as it hits that first match it pops
当它第一次匹配时就弹出
out so if you say is your catch-all that
所以如果你说是你的全部
everybody has access to anything left
每个人都可以使用剩下的任何东西
but you put that first everybody will
但是你首先把每个人都会
have access to everything which is
有权使用一切
generally a bad thing right so I'm gonna
通常是一件坏事，所以我要
authorize requests I'm gonna use MVC
授权我要使用MVC的请求
matchers so that we can use spring
匹配器，以便我们可以使用Spring
expression language to handle some of
表达语言来处理一些
the matching here I'm going to let's see
我将在这里找到匹配项
go to our admin pages right so anything
正确访问我们的管理页面
admin or sub pages and then I'm going to
管理或子页面，然后我要
verify that this this request this
验证此请求此
person has the role of user no actually
人实际上没有用户角色
for admin we want them to have the role
对于管理员，我们希望他们扮演角色
of admin right and we want to then
的管理权，我们想然后
authorize requests
授权请求
well actually any requests from here on
那么实际上从这里开始的任何请求
out right so any requests authenticated
正确，因此任何请求都已通过身份验证
and that should be good actually though
这实际上应该很好
since we're specifying this and we're
因为我们指定了这个并且
overriding that kind of default behavior
覆盖这种默认行为
that spring security provides work for
Spring Security 性为
us we also want to do it and form login
我们我们也想这样做并形成登录名
so we get our login and logout forms and
这样我们就获得了登录和注销表格，
we also want to do HTTP basic so if it's
我们也想做HTTP基本的，所以如果
non use non browser user agent that's
不使用非浏览器用户代理
covered as well so if I'm still going
也包括在内，所以如果我仍然要去
through HTTP I for instance so I'm gonna
例如，通过HTTP我将
go ahead and restart that one more time
继续并重新启动一次
and we'll quickly show how that all
我们将快速展示这一切
comes together and then we'll go to the
在一起，然后我们去
next step so far so good right I mean
到目前为止，到目前为止，一切都很好，我的意思是
this kind of does make sense when you
当您
step through it so let's go now to our
一步一步来，让我们现在进入我们的
page here let me refresh Markos password
让我刷新Markos密码的页面
oh well actually did I oh yeah yeah
哦，其实我是吗，是的，是的
because I forgot I was doing the
因为我忘了我在做
everyone thing oh that looks much better
每个人的东西哦，看起来好多了
so we've authenticated Markos has access
因此我们已经认证了Markos有权访问
he has he's authorized to see the
他有权查看
everyone page and all it's good the
每个人的页面，一切都很好
admin page and and here is exactly what
管理页面，这正是
we expect in this case as well it just
我们也希望在这种情况下
shows that it's forbidden with a status
表明它是禁止状态
code of 403 we don't want to provide
我们不想提供的403代码
excessive information to potential
潜在的过多信息
attackers right we just want to say nope
攻击者吧，我们只想说不
you can't go here so let's go back out
你不能去这里所以我们回去
now and we'll log out and we'll see if
现在，我们将注销，然后查看是否
Laurie has any better luck so let's see
劳里（Laurie）的运气更好，让我们来看看
Laurie and Laurie has a strong password
Laurie和Laurie的密码很强
don't tell anyone
不要告诉任何人
nope well actually typing counts so
很好，实际上打字很重要
let's see strong password uh-oh
让我们看看安全性高的密码
once again I did the wrong thing here so
我再次在这里做错了事
let's see everyone yes okay so Laurie's
让我们一起来看看大家，好吧，Laurie's
in there so let's go out and see if she
在那边，让我们出去看看她
can access the admin page and of course
可以访问管理页面，当然
she can more he's an administrator good
她可以更多，他是一个管理员好
thing to aspire to for all of us right
对我们所有人都渴望的事情
so she's in so this is a very quick run
所以她在，所以这是一个非常快的过程
through a form based authentication now
现在通过基于表单的身份验证
spring security makes this almost
Spring Security 性使这几乎
trivially easy to do right not bad it's
简单容易做对不坏
a good thing to get started with easily
轻松入门是一件好事
and quickly so let's log out there and
很快，让我们退出那里，
then let's let's close this out and
然后让我们结束这个
let's go on to the next step the next
让我们继续下一步
part of our adventure everyone's still
我们冒险的一部分，每个人都还是
with me oh good okay if you need to get
和我一起哦，好吧，如果你需要得到
coffee that's fine I only had a pot and
好的咖啡，我只有一壶，
a half before I came here this morning
今天早上我来这里之前一半
so I'm feeling it look pretty little
所以我觉得它看起来很少
subdued but but if you need to get up
柔和，但如果您需要起床
and grab coffee that's fine just bring
拿来没事的咖啡
me one too okay alright so I'm going to
我一个也很好，所以我要
start off by creating an OID C or an
首先创建一个OID C或一个
open ID connect application or service
打开ID连接应用程序或服务
and and I promised I would explain this
我保证我会解释这个
and I hadn't gotten back to it so let me
我还没回来，所以让我
just stop here who's here is heard of
只是停在这里听说过这里的人
OAuth to grow auth in general right in
OAuth一般会在
the bad old days before OAuth in the
OAuth之前的糟糕旧时光
vast and distant past we had a kind of a
广阔而遥远的过去，我们有一种
very bad mixture of ways that companies
公司的混合方式很差
organizations individual developers
组织个人开发人员
would try to grant access and and obtain
会尝试授予访问权限并获取
access on your behalf to your resources
代表您访问您的资源
so I like to use the example that
所以我喜欢用这个例子
actually our friends at octa use and and
实际上，我们在八达通的朋友使用和
it's Yelp anyone use the Yelp
是Yelp，有人用Yelp
application it's one of my favorites
应用程序是我的最爱之一
anytime you go to a new city or even
每当你去一个新城市甚至
just a different part of your city yeah
只是你城市的另一部分
you can check out what restaurants are
你可以看看什么餐馆
nearby and other stuff too but I always
附近和其他东西，但我总是
just go for the food obviously
只是去吃饭
so Yelp lets you kind of scope out the
所以Yelp可以让您扩大范围
the food places eating places around and
食物的地方，周围的饮食场所和
then you can post like I checked in here
然后您可以像我在这里签到一样发帖
and
和
like Foursquare and what-have-you but I
像Foursquare和您拥有什么，但我
checked in here your friends can see
在这里签到，您的朋友可以看到
that they can say hey look mark found a
他们可以说嘿表情标记发现了一个
new new taco place so this is good you
新的新炸玉米饼的地方，所以这对你有好处
know and he rated it really well let's
知道，他对它的评价很好，让我们
check that out and nobody follows me
检查一下，没有人跟着我
anyway it's fine
反正很好
but Yelp offers that capability and they
但是Yelp提供了这种功能，他们
have since before the days of OAuth they
从OAuth时代开始
used to do this really terrible thing
曾经做过这样一件非常可怕的事情
and it wasn't their fault it was just
这不是他们的错，只是
the state of the industry as it was
当时的行业状况
there wasn't a clean and easy way to to
没有一种干净便捷的方法
delegate authorization cleanly right so
完全授权授权
what they would do is they would say
他们会说
Marco's you you want to use Yelp right
Marcos，您想要正确使用Yelp
what do you what's your email provider
你是什​​么你的电子邮件提供商
is it Yahoo Gmail AOL okay so Gmail it
Yahoo Gmail AOL可以吗，Gmail吗？
is so so what's your Gmail don't tell me
是这样，您的Gmail不告诉我什么
yeah but what's your Gmail account never
是的，但是您永远不会使用什么Gmail帐户
I'll use my account mine's marked out
我将使用我标记的我的帐户
heckler gmail.com hey that's great
heckler gmail.com嘿，太好了
what's your password because next we're
您的密码是什么，因为接下来我们是
going to just harvest your contacts so
只是收获你的联系人，所以
we can establish those contacts on your
我们可以在您的联系人上建立联系
behalf then we'll get rid of it will log
代表那么我们将摆脱它会记录
out and we'll get rid of your password
出去，我们将删除您的密码
wink and and then you we're fine and
眨眼，然后你我们很好，
that sounds truly terrible because he is
这听起来真的很可怕，因为他是
truly terrible but when there's no way
真的很糟糕，但是当没有办法
you know standard way of doing it you
你知道这样做的标准方法
kind of work with what you have right so
与您所拥有的权利一起工作
Yelp did this as many other companies
Yelp和其他许多公司一样做到了
did as well this after a point you might
你可能会做完这一点
say well everyone should see this is how
说得好，每个人都应该看到这是怎么回事
bad it is and come up with something so
不好，想出点什么
they did oh off I lost 100 Othman was
他们做了哦，我输了100奥斯曼
well truly terrible as well so oauth2
真的很糟糕，所以oauth2
quickly followed right and oauth2 came
很快跟随正确，oauth2来了
up came in with the promise of
带着诺言进来
establishing a clean and easy way to
建立一个干净，容易的方法
delegate authorization right it's your
委托授权是您的
authorizations what what this
授权这是什么
application has access to on your behalf
应用程序可以代表您访问
the problem was it really didn't cover
问题是它确实没有涵盖
that whole authentication side so there
整个身份验证方面
were all kinds of bolt ons and changes
各种各样的变化和变化
and and extra capabilities added that
并且额外的功能增加了
weren't really standard eventually some
最终不是真正的标准
folks came together some organizations
人们聚集了一些组织
came together and create an open ID
一起创建一个开放的ID
connect which handles the authentication
连接处理身份验证
side of that it's kind of a shim on top
侧面是上面的垫片
of OAuth 2 so that both two can handle
的OAuth 2，以便两个都可以处理
the authorization open ID connect drop
授权开放ID连接放置
authentication pull off two for
身份验证完成两个
authorization so that's why I kind of
授权，所以这就是为什么
draw the distinction you you see them
画出你看到他们的区别
use together
一起使用
but you know they are in effect distinct
但您知道它们实际上是截然不同的
so I'm going to create a login service
所以我要创建一个登录服务
and we're going to use Open ID connect
我们将使用Open ID connect
to log in to what we need to and grant
登录到我们需要的并授予
or so that we can in turn then grant
否则我们可以依次授予
authorization to see certain things so I
授权看某些东西，所以我
already have my web dependency in my
我已经有了我的网络依赖
security dependency I'm also going to
安全依赖性我也要去
bring in my reactive web dependency and
引入我的反应式网络依赖关系
that's because that gets me the reactive
那是因为那让我反应灵敏
web client we're not going to delve into
网络客户端，我们不打算深入研究
the reactive world but web client
反应式世界，但Web客户端
handles both reactive and nonreactive
处理反应性和非反应性
interactions with different services so
与不同服务的互动
it's kind of the way forward so I want
这是前进的方向，所以我想
to bring that in and I'm going to
把它带进去，我要去
generate that project and then once
生成那个项目，然后一次
again we'll go out and we'll unzip that
再次，我们将出去，我们将其解压缩
and we'll open that as well and while
我们也会同时打开它
that comes up
那来了
ah the suspense builds okay so all right
啊，悬念建立了，好吧
so let me let me close that out and go
所以我让我把它关掉然后走
to presentation mode again what come on
再次进入演示模式
IntelliJ there we go
IntelliJ我们去了
nope there we go
不，我们去
so wrong way ah intelligent you're
这么错误的方式啊，聪明的你
killing me okay
杀了我好
like I said IntelliJ works a treat until
就像我说的IntelliJ可以请客
you have multiple projects open in
您有多个项目正在打开
presentation mode and then it just kind
演示模式，然后就好了
of throws a little bit of a fit well I
有点适合我
have a I have a request in for this an
我有一个要求
issue sadly it's it's not gone very far
可悲的是它还没有走很远
yet so and that's pretty much as much my
但是，这差不多是我的
fault as anything so so we're going to
都是错，所以我们要
create our login service here and let's
在这里创建我们的登录服务，让我们
see the first thing I want to do is go
看到我想做的第一件事就是去
to my palm I do actually need to bring
我确实需要带到我的手掌上
in a few other dependencies that aren't
在其他一些不是
brought in by default from the spring
从春季默认引入
initializer so I'm going to bring in my
初始化程序，所以我要带上我的
open ID connect dependencies here and
在这里打开ID连接依赖关系
that just gets me a few extra
那让我多了一些
dependencies like spring security config
像spring security config这样的依赖
which gives me the ability to do my
这使我有能力去做我的
security configuration via Java config
通过Java config进行安全性配置
and make this application an oauth2
并将此应用程序设为oauth2
client go off to Jose which is the
客户去了何塞
JavaScript object signing an encryption
JavaScript对象签署加密
library and then octa I wanted to bring
库，然后我想带八度
in the octave starter because it's one
在八度启动器中，因为它是一个
of the things I'm going to use for a 180
我将要使用180的东西
connect and two so the next thing I'm
连接和两个，所以我接下来
going to do is go to my application
要做的就是转到我的应用程序
about properties file which is where you
关于属性文件，这是您所在的位置
put your kind of sensible defaults your
把你的明智的默认
startup defaults for your application
应用程序的启动默认值
I'm actually going to change this from a
我实际上是要从
properties based key value key value to
基于属性的键值
a yamo file so I can structure this a
一个yamo文件，所以我可以构造一个
little nice more nicely I just that's my
好一点，好一点，我就是我
preference and then I'm going to bring
偏好，然后我要带
in my configuration there now these are
在我的配置中，现在有
some basic configuration settings I've
我已经完成的一些基本配置设置
got my client ID and secret for Google
得到了我的客户ID和Google的秘密
and octa Google and Facebook are handled
和八谷Google和Facebook被处理
out of the box of spring' security
开箱即用的Spring Security 防护
Facebook's not my cup of tea I don't
Facebook不是我的茶，我不是
recommend you use it just because that's
建议您使用它只是因为
me but it is support is there and it's a
我，但那里是支持，这是一个
excellent way of authenticating as well
也是一种很好的身份验证方法
and and of course octave provides some
并且当然八度音提供了一些
great tie-ins as well
很棒的搭配
and the issuer URI is is again for the
发行者URI再次用于
issuing your your bearer tokens so here
发行您的不记名令牌，所以在这里
in case anybody's concerned about the
万一有人担心
client secret as long as you create an
客户秘密，只要您创建
application that routes back to
路由回的应用程序
localhost:8080 go crazy anyway okay so
本地主机：8080还是会发疯吧
let's go to our main application class
让我们进入主要的应用程序类
and then let's again start off with
然后让我们再次开始
creating our endpoint rest controller
创建我们的端点 rest controller
class so this will be our oh i DC
上课，所以这将是我们的天哪
controller controller and we're gonna
控制器控制器，我们要
keep this pretty simple as well so let's
保持这个非常简单，所以让我们
see so let's see get mapping slash
看到所以让我们来看看获得映射斜线
[Music]
[音乐]
string hello return hello so well do you
字符串你好返回你好吗
hello spring I oh yeah typing is a thing
你好春天我哦，是的，打字是一回事
spring I oh yes we're excited okay so
春天，我哦，是的，我们很兴奋，所以
let's just start off with this really
让我们从这个开始吧
quickly so we can see what happens even
快速，所以我们甚至可以看到发生了什么
at this very basic level we've done a
在这个非常基础的水平上，我们已经完成了
bit of well on our behalf largely but a
代表我们很好的一点，但是
bit of configuration with our
与我们的配置
dependencies and then our settings and
依赖关系，然后是我们的设置和
that we created in our application that
我们在应用程序中创建的
yeah Mille so now if we go to localhost
是的，米勒，所以现在如果我们转到本地主机
8080 we can see that we have a couple
8080我们可以看到我们有一对
options because again we've specified to
选项，因为我们再次指定
open ID connect providers hero auth to
打开ID将提供商英雄身份验证连接到
providers so we've got octa here at the
提供者，所以我们在这里
top and we've got Google now I'm gonna
顶部，我们现在有了Google，我要
log in with both just to kind of show
两者都登录只是为了展示
you a couple neat things I think so if
你几件整洁的东西，我想如果
we log in with Google it's asking hey
我们用谷歌登录问
what is your your account so mark that
您的帐户是什么？
Heckler and then it's asking my password
黑客，然后询问我的密码
of course so so let's see oops let's see
当然，所以让我们来看看哎呀，我们来看看
there ah perfect so here we have that
那里是完美的，所以我们在这里
kind of super level of security right
一种超高水平的担保权
it's prompting us because I have
提示我们，因为我有
two-factor authentication established
建立两因素身份验证
and configured on my Google ID which if
并在我的Google ID上进行了配置，如果
you have a corporate arrangement with
你与公司有安排
Google for your Gmail on Google suite
在Google Suite上使用Google for Gmail
you may have this already you may have
你可能已经有了这个
had this be a requirement for you so I'm
这是您的要求吗，我
going to plug in my yubikey and just
要插入我的yubikey，
touch that
碰那个
and just touch that there we go okay so
只需触摸一下，我们就可以了，所以
so we're all set so now we've gotten two
所以我们都准备好了，现在我们有两个
factor authentication effectively for
有效的要素认证
free right because that's part of our
自由权利，因为那是我们的一部分
arrangement here a part of our
在这里安排我们的一部分
configuration so we're in so that's kind
配置，这样我们就可以了
of nice
好
I'm also going to just log out here and
我也要在这里登出
go back and try it again through octa
返回并通过octa再次尝试
nacht I don't have to FAU configured but
我不需要配置FAU，但是
we just do this and sign in and you can
我们只要这样做并登录，您就可以
see it works pretty much the same way
看到它的工作方式几乎相同
right so hello is Springer el nice okay
好的，你好，Springer el很好吗
but it really doesn't get us anything
但这真的没有给我们任何东西
because at this point all we've done is
因为在这一点上我们所做的就是
authenticate typically what happens
通常验证发生的情况
you'll have resource servers which will
您将拥有资源服务器
provide resources right that you want to
提供您想要的资源
access via your login via your
通过您的登录名访问
credentials so we want to go ahead at
凭证，所以我们想继续
this point and create a resource server
至此，创建资源服务器
so we can access that res svr
这样我们就可以访问该res svr
I don't need my web client I'll be using
我不需要我要使用的网络客户端
that to get to our resource server here
到这里我们的资源服务器
momentarily so let's go ahead and save
暂时，让我们继续保存
that and go here come on there we go
那去那里来吧我们去
open and we'll do that as well okay so
打开，我们也会这样做的，所以
the first thing once again I'm going to
我再次要去的第一件事
do is go to my palm and I'm gonna add in
要做的就是去我的手掌，我要添加
the few dependencies that I need to add
我需要添加的几个依赖项
just to give me what I want here for my
只是为了给我我想要的东西
resource server dependencies and again
资源服务器依存关系
very similar spring security config for
非常相似的spring安全配置
Java config this time we've got the the
这次的Java配置
library for OAuth 2 resource server so
OAuth 2资源服务器的库
we can provide that bit of capabilities
我们可以提供一些功能
out of the gate both to Jose once again
走出大门，再次回到何塞
and octa once again so let's see we'll
再八点，让我们来看看
do that we'll go to our application
做到这一点，我们将转到我们的应用程序
properties and again I'm going to rename
属性，然后我将重命名
this again just as a convenience
再次为了方便
yamo and then we'll bring in our
yamo，然后我们将我们的
configuration properties there as well
那里的配置属性
so yeah so let's go we're five minutes
所以是的，我们走了五分钟
tons of time I'm kidding this is going
很多时间，我在开玩笑
to be a bit of a stretch but we can do
有点紧张，但我们可以做到
it right we have the the wind at our
是的，我们有风
backs okay so I'm going to create a rest
可以，所以我要休息一下
controller I'm going to set up a default
控制器，我要设置一个默认值
mapping here of resources resources
在此处映射资源资源
class
类
resource controller and let's see get
资源控制器，让我们看看
mapping / something will say that's
映射/可能会说
something and string get something
一些东西和弦得到一些东西
return this is something right so this
返回这是正确的事情，所以这
is our resource we're just going to use
是我们将要使用的资源
that as an example but that's not it
举例来说，不是
right we wanted something a bit more
对，我们想要更多
impressive than that
比那令人印象深刻
so in this case what I actually want to
所以在这种情况下我实际上想要
do is be able to check out our claims so
能够检查我们的索赔，所以
we can see what our claims are here so I
我们可以看到我们的主张在这里，所以我
might return a string get claims and I'm
可能会返回一个字符串获取声明，而我
going to actually bring in our
真正带来我们的
authentication principle which is a jot
认证原理
a JSON web token right and this is the
JSON Web令牌权利，这是
way that instead of actually having to
这样，而不是实际上不得不
pass our authorization our credentials
通过我们的授权我们的凭证
back and forth among various services
在各种服务之间来回
once we've established that connection
建立联系后
we've established that we are who we say
我们已经确定我们就是我们所说的人
we are we can use that to provide a JSON
我们可以使用它来提供JSON
web token jot I don't ask me on the
网络令牌记号我不问我
pronunciation and I didn't make it up
的发音，我没有弥补
but we're gonna pass that jot and and
但是我们要通过那个记号，然后
allow our resource server to use that to
允许我们的资源服务器使用它来
see what claims we have what scopes we
看看我们有什么主张我们有什么范围
have so there we go jawed and we'll just
有，所以我们要忍受，我们只是
do a return job get claims to string and
做一个回头工作得到要求的字符串和
that's sufficient again for our purposes
足以满足我们的目的
and then we'll do a get mapping it would
然后我们将进行映射
be nice to see who is the who's the
很高兴看到谁是谁
subject who is the email address what
主题谁是电子邮件地址什么
email address is associated with this
电子邮件地址与此相关
particular authors or authenticated user
特定作者或经过身份验证的用户
so we'll do that string get subject
所以我们将字符串作为主题
return jot oh haha actually helps if you
返回记号哦哈哈，如果您有帮助，
inject that authentication principle and
注入身份验证原理并
that way we can do a get subject perfect
这样我们就可以做到完美
okay so now oh what's that line oh thank
好吧，现在哦，那条线是什么，谢谢
you very much okay email we'll change
您非常好，我们会更改电子邮件
that that'll work a little better right
那会更好一点吧
thank you very much I when I start
我非常感谢你，当我开始
hearing things I hear occasionally stuff
听到我偶尔听到的东西
from behind this wall and I was trying
从这堵墙后面，我正在尝试
to figure out where that was coming from
弄清楚那是从哪里来的
so okay so that works or should work a
好吧，这样可以工作或应该工作
little bit better all right so now I
好一点了好吧，现在我
need to let's go ahead and restart that
需要让我们继续并重新启动
and what I want to do at this point is
我现在要做的是
go back to my open ID controller because
回到我的开放ID控制器，因为
what we need to do now is create a a web
我们现在需要做的是创建一个网站
client beam web client web client client
客户端Beam Web客户端Web客户端客户端
can't even type now it's just all gone
现在甚至无法输入，一切都消失了
downhill so the thing I need to do in
下坡，所以我需要做的事情
order to be able to pass that jot so
为了能够通过那个记号
that we can access that via our resource
我们可以通过我们的资源访问它
server is to create a filter here so in
服务器将在此处创建过滤器
this case we want a servlet go off to
在这种情况下，我们希望servlet转到
authorize client exchange filter
授权客户交换过滤器
function just rolls off the tongue right
功能只是滚开舌头
so it's so easy we'll shorten that a bit
所以很简单，我们将其缩短一点
to just filter function and we will use
只是过滤功能，我们将使用
that too will do a servlet both to
也会同时做一个servlet
authorize exchange client exchange
授权交流客户交流
filter function so new and that actually
过滤器功能如此新颖，实际上
can take a couple of parameters a client
可以给客户几个参数
registration repository and it ought to
注册库，它应该
authorize client repository now one
现在授权客户端存储库
actually maintains some some basic
实际上保持一些基本
registration information for your
您的注册信息
potential clients that you're going to
您要去的潜在客户
use the other is your a lot to authorize
使用其他是您的很多授权
client so so actually I'm going to again
客户，所以实际上我要再次
use spring boots Auto config which
使用 spring boot 自动配置
actually has these beans created on your
实际上是在您的计算机上创建了这些bean
behalf based upon your dependencies once
一次根据您的依赖关系
again and I'm going to pass those in so
再次，我将通过这些
let's see we need a let's now have sit
让我们看看我们需要让我们现在坐下
here monologuing and I forgot it's a
在这里独白，我忘了
client registration repository so client
客户注册资料库，因此客户
registration repository and we'll just
注册存储库，我们将只是
call this client repo actually I'll just
叫这个客户回购实际上我只是
call this a registration repo for short
简称为注册回购
and then a an auth to authorize client
然后是一个授权来授权客户端
repository and we'll just call that our
存储库，我们将其称为
client repo repo and that's sufficient
客户回购回购，这就足够了
and then we'll go down and in our
然后我们下去，进入我们的
servlet in our filter function I'll just
我将在我们的过滤器功能中使用servlet
pass those in and see client repo and
将这些信息传递给客户，并查看客户回购和
that's sufficient there to create our
足以创建我们的
servlet
小服务程序
I've read our filter function let's just
我已经阅读了我们的过滤器功能
leave it at that so I'm gonna take that
留在那儿，我要拿那个
filter function and set the default I'll
过滤器功能并设置默认值
off to authorize client to true but that
授权客户真实，但那
doesn't say hey look for our logged in
不说嘿寻找我们的登录状态
user that's actually what we're wanting
用户正是我们想要的
to use for our authorize client in many
用于许多我们的授权客户
cases that's the case but it is
情况是这样，但事实是
something that you can opt out of and
您可以选择退出的内容
but again it kind of makes sense that
但同样有道理的是
whoever's logged in you want access to
要登录的人
their resources so in this case we'll
他们的资源，所以在这种情况下，我们将
set that to true and then we will create
将其设置为true，然后我们将创建
return a new actually we'll do a web
返回一个新的，实际上我们会做一个网站
client dot builder and then we'll assign
客户点生成器，然后我们将分配
a base URL in this case we're going to
在这种情况下，我们将使用基本网址
be accessing a resource server which is
正在访问资源服务器
at localhost 8080 one slash resources
在本地主机8080处一个斜杠资源
for our base URL resources yeah that's
对于我们的基本URL资源，是的
good and then I'm going to apply our
好，然后我将应用我们的
filter function dot go off to
过滤功能点转到
configuration which provides that go off
提供关闭的配置
to authentication or capability via our
通过我们的身份验证或功能
web client and then we'll build that and
网络客户端，然后我们将其构建
then let's inject our web client here so
然后在这里注入我们的网络客户端
private final web client client and then
私人最终Web客户端客户端，然后
let's create some endpoints so we can
让我们创建一些端点，以便我们可以
access our resource server and then
访问我们的资源服务器，然后
we're off to the races right okay so get
我们要去比赛了，好吧
mapping slash something string get
映射斜杠某字符串获取
something return client dot get dot and
东西返回客户点得到点和
we we have our base URI which is enough
我们有足够的基本URI
for what we need right here we're gonna
在这里我们需要的是
bring this back the body of our response
把这带回我们回应的主体
as a mono which is a zero or one
作为零或一的单声道
publisher reactive publisher and we're
发布商反应式发布商，我们
bringing back a string right in this
带回一个正确的字符串
case oops
情况
string class and then we're just going
字符串类，然后我们就去
to convert that to the basic string
将其转换为基本字符串
right because this is imperative code at
对，因为这是命令式代码
this point it's easy to go from
这一点很容易
non-blocking to blocking not so much the
非阻塞的不是那么阻塞
other way around and then I'm going to
反过来，然后我要
do a get mapping slash claims so we can
做一个映射斜杠声明，以便我们可以
retrieve our claim string get claims
检索我们的索赔字符串获取索赔
returned client get we need to add on
返回的客户得到我们需要添加
our URI of slash claims retrieve body de
我们的斜杠URI声明检索主体de
mano
马诺
once again we're returning a string and
再次，我们返回一个字符串，
we'll just block to grab the actual
我们将阻止获取实际
string out of the motto once again get
串出格言再次得到
mapping / email string get email return
映射/电子邮件字符串获取电子邮件返回
client dot get uri email retrieve body
客户端点获取uri电子邮件检索正文
de mano once again we're just returning
de mano再次回到
a string in this case and block now one
在这种情况下是一个字符串，现在阻止一个
thing that I forgot to do so I'm gonna
我忘了做的事，我要
go back over and do that while that's
回去做那是
restarting is that our resource ur
重新启动是我们的资源
resource server say that three times
资源服务器说三遍
fast I need to perforate a bit of
快速，我需要打孔
customer customized configuration for
客户定制的配置
our security adapter once again so
我们的安全适配器再次如此
enable web security class security
启用网络安全级别的安全性
config config extends web security
config config扩展了Web安全性
configure adapter once again we're going
再次配置适配器，我们要
to override our configure there we go
覆盖我们的配置，我们去
and actually here we can just start
实际上在这里我们可以开始
right in here HTTP dot authorize
就在这里HTTP点授权
requests we want to use MVC matches once
要求我们一次使用MVC匹配
again for our claims has authority in
再次因为我们的主张在
this case for OAuth and we need to have
对于OAuth，我们需要
our scope open ID in this case so we can
在这种情况下，我们的范围开放ID
access what we need there and authorize
访问那里我们需要的东西并授权
requests NBC matchers once again in this
在此再次请求NBC匹配者
case for email has authority we're just
电子邮件的情况下有权力，我们只是
gonna go with a scope email right and
会正确使用范围电子邮件，
[Music]
[音乐]
let's see-oh off to resource server John
让我们来看看，哦，去资源服务器John
so we can have jot support here as well
所以我们也可以在这里获得支持
so let's go ahead and run that and now
所以让我们继续运行，现在
let's go for the big finale and we're
我们去大结局，我们
over so I need to wrap this up quickly
结束，所以我需要快速结束
so we can go eat right yeah so alright
这样我们就可以去吃饭了
so let's go back up here and know yes I
所以让我们回到这里，知道是的，我
believe that up nicely makes a little
相信上升能带来一点好处
hard to read there we'll just go in via
很难阅读，我们只能通过
octave Oh
八度哦
let's see I need to log out first
让我们看看我需要先注销
Genesis latch logout yes
创世记闩锁注销是
and then let's login with octo once
然后让我们用octo登录一次
again
再次
okay let's do this the hard way
好吧，让我们用困难的方式做到这一点
local host 8080 there we go
本地主机8080我们去了
mark sweet
马克甜
alright so hello spring i/o now if we
好吧，你好，春天，如果我们
want to go to something just to see if
想要去看看只是为了看看
we're passing through to our resource
我们正在传递我们的资源
server oh okay
服务器哦，好的
so what am i doing what have I got here
所以我在做什么我到了这里
Oh resources something yeah that's uh
哦，资源是的，嗯
that's just well that's fine let's just
很好，很好，让我们
do that
去做
so resources actually no I can't do that
所以资源实际上不，我不能那样做
because I mapped it wrong
因为我把它映射错了
we'll just cut right to the chase here
我们就在这里追逐
claims I can go back and restart this
声称我可以返回并重新启动
but this is much cleaner and just this
但这要干净得多
is the part I wanted to show you anyway
是我想告诉你的部分
so here we're getting our claims off of
所以在这里，我们得到了我们的要求
our resource server so we're well via
我们的资源服务器，所以我们很好
our resource server so we're seeing what
我们的资源服务器，所以我们看到了什么
claims we've extended to that we can see
我们已经扩展到可以看到的声明
that we have scopes of email address
我们有电子邮件地址的范围
phone open ID and profile we can see the
手机的开放ID和个人资料，我们可以看到
subject is me mark at the hecklers at
主题是我在
org now if I go and just check the email
组织，如果我去，只是检查电子邮件
we can see that that pulls that back
我们可以看到将其拉回
fine so everything is working we've
很好，所以一切正常，我们已经
connected via open ID we've established
通过我们建立的开放ID连接
our identity our authentication there we
我们的身份我们的身份验证我们
then authorize certain endpoints based
然后根据
upon certain capabilities provided or
根据提供的某些功能或
expressed in our jot so let's go back
表达在我们的记号中，让我们回去
and wrap up and let's go eat so
包起来，我们去吃饭吧
everything you saw here and a bit more
您在这里看到的一切以及更多
is in this top repository here spring
春天在这个顶级仓库中
security for noobs please join in please
菜鸟安全，请加入
check it out if you see anything that
检查一下是否看到任何东西
I've missed or hey would you do this or
我想念或嘿，你会这样做还是
why didn't you do this please let me
你为什么不这样做，请让我
know happy to take feedback again
知道很高兴再次接受反馈
there's only so much I can cram in so I
我只能塞很多东西，所以我
try to kind of hit the high points but
尝试达到高点，但
if there's something important you feel
如果你有重要的事情
like glossed over let me know because I
像被蒙蔽了一样让我知道，因为我
want to continue to iterate and improve
希望继续迭代和改进
on this the spring security main site is
在此，Spring Security 性主要站点是
right there at the bottom
就在底部
spring i/o project spring security great
春季I / O项目Spring Security 性很好
set of resources there as well
还有那里的资源
thanks for coming and let's go enjoy
感谢您的光临，让我们一起去享受
screen
屏幕
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]